[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does short-waisted mean?", "correct_answer": "It means your torso is short.", "incorrect_answers": ["It means your waist is shorter than your head.", "It means your shorts need replacing.", "It means your waist is not very high above the ground."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The program components named coroutines generalize the widely known subroutines by allowing multiple return values.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who provided the voice for Lewis in the movie Meet the Robinsons?", "correct_answer": "Both of these", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Jordan Fry", "Daniel Hansen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1984 movie Red Dawn, Colonel Bella, the commander of the invading forces in Calumet, was an officer in what nations invading army?", "correct_answer": "Cuba", "incorrect_answers": ["Soviet Union", "Mexico", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although seemingly different, the diamond and the graphite are both allotropes of one and the same chemical element. Which one?", "correct_answer": "Carbon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Iron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elmer Valo, a Major League Baseball player and coach, is one of the few American major leaguers born in this country.", "correct_answer": "The Czech Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Surinam", "Serbia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Princess Diaries, Lillys public access television program is called Shut Up and Kiss.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Latt\u00e9?", "correct_answer": "Espresso plus aerated milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee plus aerated milk", "Coffee plus aerated milk plus chocolate", "Espresso plus aerated milk plus chocolate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress, who plays Leah on Juno, is more famous for her roles in Kidnapped and United 93.", "correct_answer": "Olivia Thirlby", "incorrect_answers": ["Dana Clarke", "Dana Clark", "Dina Twoomy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did early Greeks believe lightning was?", "correct_answer": "The weapon of Zeus", "incorrect_answers": ["A warning from Minerva", "The sign of death", "A symbol of good fortune"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who helped invent the blender?", "correct_answer": "Fred Waring", "incorrect_answers": ["Carl Sontheimer", "Carl Frederick Winson", "Gene Armor Polly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spanish is an official language of this African country.", "correct_answer": "Equatorial Guinea", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "Mozambique", "Chad"]}]